Guide to the James Perkins papers,1963-1969.
Perkins, James papers,1963-1969.
- Series III. 1967-1969
  - Rockcastle, Verne N. et al, Correspondence re Student-Faculty Activism. Student conduct; Student activism., 1967 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - SA-SL Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    Saltonstall, Leverett; Scarborough, Ethel T. Leverett Saltonstall Jr. Memorial Fund; Sardis Expedition.
  - SA-SL Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    Schaetzel, J. Robert; Scheetz, Virginia; Schwartz, Richard J.; Scott, Alicia Onnami. David Schwartz Foundation.
  - SA-SL Miscellaneous. Seznec, Alain., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - SA-SL Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    Sindler, Allan P.; Singer, Michael N. Sigma Xi.
  - SM-SZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    Smith, Kennedy; Smith, Luther; Smith, Peter C.
  - SM-SZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    Society for College and University Planning.
  - SM-SZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    Solowey, Fred J.
  - SM-SZ Miscellaneous. Stevens, Stoddard M.; Steward, Frederick C.; Summerskill, John. Swiss Society of Sciences in the United States., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Six Universities Group., 1968 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    Bragdon, Paul E.
  - Selective Service., 1968 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    Deferments.
  - TA-TK Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Tarcov, Nathan; Taussig, J. Wright.
  - TA-TK Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Tinsley, Adrian.
  - TL-TZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Todd, Walter L.; Mercier, Harry. Cornell boat; United Fund of Tompkins County.
  - TL-TZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Trung, Nguyen Van; Trussell, John C.; Turner, James E. United Fund of Tompkins County; Center for Afro-American Studies.
  - TL-TZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Turner, James E. Center for Afro-American Studies; Institute for the Study of Society and Culture in Africa.
  - Teaching Assistants., 1968 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Today Show, 12 March 1968., 1968 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder S)
  - "To Whom It May Concern" Letters., 1963-65 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - U Miscellaneous., 1967-67 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Freeman, Orville L. United States Air Force Academy; United States Dept. of Agriculture.
  - U Miscellaneous., 1967-68 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    United States Dept. of State; Upward Bound.
  - University Commission on the Interdependence of University Regulations and Local, State and Federal Laws., 1967 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    Sindler, Allan P.; Davis, David B. Student conduct.
  - University Commission on Undergraduate Education., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    Tobias, Sheila.
  - University Commission on Undergraduate Education., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    Tobias, Sheila; Closson, B. Michael; Sproull, Robert L.
  - University Commission on Undergraduate Education., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    Tobias, Sheila; Sproull, Robert L.
  - University Commission on Undergraduate Education., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Universities Research Association, Inc. Long, Franklin A.; Wilson, Robert R. United States Atomic Energy Commission., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - V Miscellaneous., 1968-69 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    Volunteer Teachers for Africa.
  - W Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    Walker, Mark L.; Ward, J. Carlton.
  - W Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    Whyte, William Foote; Williams, Robin M.; Williams, Kenneth. Williams Commission.
  - W Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    Winter, George.
  - W Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    Wright, Theodore P.; Wu, K.C. Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation.
  - Water Pollution Laboratory, Water Resources Center., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    Dworsky, Leonard. Cornell University Water Resources and Marine Science Center.
  - XYZ Miscellaneous., 1967-68 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    Yale University.
- Series IV. 1963-1969
  - President., 1966-69 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    Corson, Dale R. Willard Straight Hall occupation; James Perkins' resignation; Law School.
  - President., 1966-69 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Kettering, Eugene W.; Olin, Spencer T. Cornell Conference Center; Ithaca City School Board.
  - President., 1966-69 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Olin, Spencer T.; Williams, Frederic A. Educational Testing Service.
  - President., 1966-69 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Administrative Assistant to the President., 1966-67 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Association of Colleges and Univs. of the State of New York., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    Ingalls, Lester W.; Palamountain, Joseph C. L.; Student conduct.
  - Association of Colleges and Univs. of the State of New York., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 31-33)
    Ingalls, Lester W.; Eikel, Robert E. Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities.
  - Association of American Universities., 1968-69 (Box 31, Folder 34-36)
  - Carnegie Corporation., 1962-68 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    Anderson, Florence; Pifer, Alan.
  - Carnegie Corporation., 1962-68 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    Morrisett, Lloyd N.; Pifer, Alan; Gardner, John W.
  - Carnegie Corporation., 1962-68 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Ford Foundation., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    Bundy, McGeorge. New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing.
  - Ford Foundation., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    Ward, F. Champion. Six Year Ph.D. Program.
  - United States Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare., . 1967-69. (Box 31, Folder 42)
    Alien, James E.; Howe, Harold. Advisory Committee on Higher Education.
  - United States Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    Howe, Harold; Gardner, John W.
  - United States Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare., 1967-69 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    Howe, Harold.
  - Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    "Toward a Program of Urban and Metropolitan Studies."
  - United States Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare Office of Education., 1967 (Box 32, Folder 2-4)
    McCarthy, Stephen A.; Winston, Oliver C.
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS)., 1968-69 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Johnson, Jay; Londner, Steve. ROTC.
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS)., 1968-69 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    MOVE; Housing.
  - Cornell University Commission of April 1968., 1968 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Materials Science Center., 1968 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Rankin, G.F.; Sack, Henri S.
  - 19-20 April 1969, Occupation of Willard Straight Hall on Parents' Weekend., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Carter, Lisle C.; Goldsen, Rose K. Students for a Democratic Society (SDS).
  - 19-20 April 1969, Occupation of Willard Straight Hall on Parents' Weekend., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Students for a Democratic Society (SDS); Barton Hall.
  - 19-20 April 1969, Occupation of Willard Straight Hall on Parents' Weekend., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Purcell, Robert W. Students for a Democratic Society (SDS).
  - Student Demonstrations., 1965-67 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Student dissent; Student demonstrations.
  - Student Demonstrations., 1965-67 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    Brewster, Kingman. Student dissent; Student demonstrations.
  - Student Demonstrations., 1965-67 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Students for Educational Transformation., 1968 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - South Africa., 1968-69 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Butler, Ronald Paul. Princeton University; Investments.
  - South Africa., 1968-69 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    Marcham, Frederick G.; Ntlabati, Gladstone. Students for a Democratic Society (SDS); African National Congress; Cornell University Commission on Investments and Public Policy; Investments.
  - South Africa., 1968-69 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    Marcham, Frederick G.; Horn, Robert T.; Morse, Chandler. African-American Institute; Cornell University Commission on Investments and Public Policy; Students for A Democratic Society (SDS); Investments.
  - South Africa. Kahn, Alfred E.; Detwiler, Bruce. Students for a Democratic Society (SDS); Investments., 1968-69 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - South Africa Symposium., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    Whyte, William Foote; Morse, Chandler; Rusk, Richard. Students for A Democratic Society (SDS); Investments.
  - National Science Foundation., 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - City of Ithaca., 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    Kiely, Jack K. Ithaca City School District; Housing; Students for A Democratic Society (SDS).
  - University Committee on Human Subjects., 1967-68 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Residential Colleges., 1967-68 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    Seznec, Alain; Closson, B. Michael.
  - Humanities Debate, L. Pearce Williams et al., 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    Brown, Stuart M.; Williams, L. Pearce; Guerlac, Henry; Sindler, Allan P. Humanities Council.
  - President's Advisory Committee on Human Rights., 1965-69 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    Reconstitution of committee.
  - Housing., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    Hall, Jackson O. Tompco Better Housing, Inc.
  - Housing., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    Hall, Jackson O.; Purcell, Robert W. Students for A Democratic Society (SDS); MOVE.
  - Housing., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    Hall, Jackson O. Tompco Better Housing, Inc.; MOVE.
  - Housing., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    MOVE; Students for A Democratic Society (SDS).
  - Housing., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    Goldman, Jack; Hall, Jackson O.
  - Select Committee on the Future of Private and Independent Higher Education in New York State., 1967-68 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    Bundy, McGeorge.
  - Rockefeller Foundation., 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    Harrar, J. George; Smith, J. Kellum.
  - The Andrew Dickson White Professors at Large., 1965-69 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    Black, Max; Frye, Northrop; Guerlac, Henry; Leakey, Louis S.B.; Aron, Raymond. Nominations.
  - The Andrew Dickson White Professors at Large., 1965-69 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    Black, Max; Carter, Elliott; Aigran, Pierre; Kac, Mark; Von Wright, Georg Henrik; Villegas, Daniel Cosio.
  - The Andrew Dickson White Professor at Large. Black, Max; McClintock, Barbara; Ashby, Eric; Leakey, Louis S.B., 1965-69 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - The Andrew Dickson White Professors at Large., 1965-69 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    Black, Max; Nabokov, Vladimir.
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation., 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    Wessell, Nils Y.
  - Provost., 1965-69 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    Corson, Dale R. University Faculty.
  - Society for the Humanities., 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    Black, Max; Mumford, Lewis; Bloom, Harold.
  - Society for the Humanities., 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    Black, Max; Frye, Northrop; Mellon, Paul.
  - Society for the Humanities., 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    Black, Max; Seznec, Alain; Koenig, Myron L.; Noyes, Nicholas H. National Endowment for the Humanities.
  - COSEP (Committee on Special Education Projects). Joseph, Gloria I.; Beck, Robert A., 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - COSEP (Committee on Special Education Projects)., 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    Joseph, Gloria I.; Beck, Robert A.; Silverman, Albert.
  - COSEP (Committee on Special Education Projects)., 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    McHugh, G. Michael; Donlon, Mary H.
  - Afro-America., 1968-69 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    Hatchett, John F.; Goldfarb, Morris; Turner, James E.; Goodwin, Stephen R.; Kennedy, W. Keith. Center for Afro-American Studies.
  - Afro- America., 1968-69 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    Jones, Tom; Haskins, Jacqueline; Kennedy, W. Keith; Turner, James E.; Messing, Gordon M. Committee on Afro-American Studies.
  - Afro-America. Turner, James E.; Morse, Chandler; Armstrong, Earl M. Afro-American Studies Program; College of Afro-American Studies (Proposed)., 1968-69 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Afro-American., 1968-69 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    Darling, Ruth W.; Cooke, W. Donald; DuBois, Paul M. COSEP; Black Ad Hoc Committee on Ithaca Education.
  - DuBois, Paul M. Puryear, Mahlon T., 1968-69 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Olin, Spencer T., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Purcell, Robert W., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    COSEP.
  - Noyes, Nicholas H., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Andrew Dickson White Professors at Large; John L. Senior Chair; Nicholas H. Noyes Professorship.
  - Johnson, Herbert P., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Leavitt, Thomas W.
  - Commission on Investments and Public Policy., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 6-8)
    Divestment; Apartheid; African-American Institute.
  - President., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Purcell, Robert W.; Turner, James E.
  - President., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    United States Selective Service.
  - President., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    "Dumbbells"; International Conference on the World Crisis in Education.
  - 17 Hay 1968 Reception., 1968 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Presidential Councilors., 1966-69 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Stevens, Stoddard M.
  - Assistants to the President., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    Eager, George B.
  - Assistants to the President., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Reports of the President., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Inventory., 1960-68 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Office of Regional Planning and Development., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 18-20)
  - Vice President for Public Affairs., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    Ramin, Richard M.; Muller, Steven. University of California at Los Angeles.
  - Vice President for Public Affairs., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    Muller, Steven? Kagan, Donald; Noll, A. Robert. Ford Foundation; Luce Foundation; Cornell University Dept. of Government.
  - Vice President for Public Affairs., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    Muller, Steven; Kane, Robert J. Xerox Corporation; Bundy Proposal.
  - Vice President for Public Affairs., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    Muller, Steven; Uris, Harold D. Ford Foundation; WHCU.
  - Vice President for Public Affairs., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    Muller, Steven; Donlon, Mary H.
  - Cornell University Council., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    Muller, Steven.
  - Vice President for Student Affairs., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    Barlow, Mark. COSEP; COSEP Cooperative for Women; CURW; Students for A Democratic Society (SDS).
  - Vice President for Student Affairs., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    COSEP; Willard Straight Hall; Sindler Commission.
  - Vice President for Planning., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    Mackesey, Thomas W. Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art; Housing.
  - Vice President for Planning., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    Pei, I.M. Low income housing; Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art; Ithaca Festival of the Arts.
  - Secretary of the Corporation and University Counsel., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    Stamp, Neal R.; Purcell, Robert W. Students for A Democratic Society (SDS); McMullen Trust; Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory; Student conduct.
  - Secretary of the Corporation and University Counsel., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    Purcell, Robert W.; Stamp, Neal R.; Corson, Dale R.; Singer, Michael N.; Wynkoop, George E. Capital Fund; Student discipline; Residential Club fire.
  - Secretary of the Corporation and University Counsel. Purcell, Robert W.; Stamp, Neal R. New York Hospital - Cornell University Medical Center; Student conduct., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Summer Work-Scholarship Program., 1968-69 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    Carter, Lisle C.; DuBois, Paul M.; Christian, Vance A.
  - Summer Work-Scholarship Program. Purcell, Robert W.; Rockefeller, David; Christian, Vance A.; DuBois, Paul M. Rockefeller Foundation., 1968-69 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Summer Work-Scholarship Program., 1968-69 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    Purcell, Robert W.; Rockefeller, David; Christian, Vance A.; DuBois, Paul M. COSEP.
  - Summer Work-Scholarship Program., 1968-69 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    Christian, Vance A.; DuBois, Paul M.
  - Orientation Program., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Dean of the Faculty., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    Miller, Robert D. University Commission on Residential Environment; Academic freedom.
  - Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art., 1967-69 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    Pel, I.M.; Leavitt, Thomas W.; Young, Martie W.; Rockwell, Mary; Murphy, Franklin; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Downing, William S.; Johnson, Herbert F. Joint Professorship between Cornell University and the Metropolitan Museum of Art; Samuel H. Kress Foundation.
  - ROTC. Blair, Howard E. Students for A Democratic Society (SDS)., 1968-69 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - ROTC., 1968-69 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - ROTC, President's Commission on Military Training., 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
    Laird, Melvin R.
  - ROTC Meeting, 26 March., 1968-69 (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
    United States Dept. of Defense.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1969 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    Moffitt, Henry K.; Purcell, Robert W.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1969 (Box 34, Folder 6-8)
    Moffitt, Henry K.; Ross, Ira G.; Schoellkopf, Paul A. Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory - Cornell University separation.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, Buffalo Meeting, 13 December 1968., 1968 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory - Cornell University separation.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1968-69 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    Purcell, Robert W.; Ross, Ira G. EDP Technology, Inc.; Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory - Cornell University separation.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Corson, Dale R.; Moffitt, Henry K. EDP Technology, Inc.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    Furnas, Clifford C.; Corson, Dale R.; Moffitt, Henry K.; O'Neal, John J. Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory - Cornell University separation.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    Corson, Dale R.; Moffitt, Henry K.; Woods, Homer H. Cornell Club in Buffalo; Batelle Memorial Institute.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    Purcell, Robert W.; Kaushagen, W.M. EDP Technology, Inc.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    Burton, John E.; Purcell, Robert W.; Stamp, Neal R.; Ross, Ira G. EDP Technology, Inc.; Cornell University Trustees Ad Hoc Committee re Separation of Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory and Cornell University.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    Ross, Ira G.; Purcell, Robert W. Cornell University Trustees Ad Hoc Committee re Separation of Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory and Cornell University
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    Ross, Ira G.; Curtiss, W. David. Cornell University Trustees Ad Hoc Committee re Separation of Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory and Cornell University.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    Curtiss, W. David; Long, Franklin A.; Ward, J. Carlton; Dean, Arthur H.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    Ross, Ira G.; Hollister, Solomon C. Cornell University Trustees Ad Hoc Committee re Separation of Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory and Cornell University.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    Wright, Theodore P.; Schultz, Andrew; Ross, Ira G.; Curtiss, W. David.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    Ross, Ira G.; Hollister, Solomon C.; Curtiss, W. David; Kahin, George McT.; Sproull, Robert L.; Sharp, Lauriston. James Perkins1 statement on Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory. Black, Max; Rossiter, Clinton; Kahin, George McT.; Wright, Theodore P.; Golay, Frank H.; Cheilek, H.A.; Orear, Jay; Curtiss, W. David; Dean, Arthur H. James Perkins1 statement on Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - University Center for Research in Education., 1967 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Afro-American Studies, Working Papers., 1968-69 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    DuBois, Paul M. Afro-American Society.
  - Afro-American Studies, Working Papers., 1968-69 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    Joseph, Gloria I.; Turner, James E. Afro-American Society.
  - Afro- American Studies, Working Papers., 1968-69 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    Afro-American Society.
  - Correspondence re the Resignation of James Perkins., 1969 (Box 34, Folder 28-39)
  - Letters to Robert W. Purcell re James Perkins' Resignation., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Board of Trustees re James Perkins' Resignation and events of the Spring of 1969., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 2-4)
  - Robert W. Purcell Correspondence., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    Ashmead, Katharine V.; LaFeber, Walter F.
  - Correspondence re Willard Straight Hall occupation and the events of Spring 1969/"Challenge to Governance."
    - Alabama., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Alaska., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Arizona., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Arkansas., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Bolivia., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - California., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 11-13)
    - Chicago., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Colorado., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Connecticut., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Delaware., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Florida., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 18-19)
    - Georgia., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Idaho., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Illinois., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Indiana., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Iowa., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Ithaca., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Kansas., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Kentucky., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Louisiana., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Maine., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Massachusetts., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Maryland., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Michigan., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Minnesota., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Mississippi., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Missouri., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Montana., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Nevada., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - New Hampshire., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - New Jersey., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 39-40)
    - New Mexico., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - New York City., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 42-44)
    - New York State., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 45-49)
    - North Carolina., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - North Dakota., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Ohio., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Oklahoma., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Oregon., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - Pennsylvania., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 55-56)
    - Puerto Rico., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - Rhode Island., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - South Carolina., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - South Dakota., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - Syracuse., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - Tennessee., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - Texas., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 63-64)
    - Utah., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Vermont., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Vietnam., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Virginia., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Washington., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Washington, D.C., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - West Virginia., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Wisconsin., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Wyoming., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 10-11)
    - Clippings - Arizona., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Clippings - Arkansas., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Clippings - California., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Clippings - Chicago., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Clippings - Colorado., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Clippings - Connecticut., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Clippings - Delaware., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Clippings - Florida., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Clippings - Georgia., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Clippings - Illinois., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Clippings - Iowa., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Clippings - Ithaca., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Clippings - Kansas., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Clippings - Kentucky., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Clippings - Louisiana., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Clippings - Maine., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 27)